http://www.sitebits.com/privacy.html

Home » Our Privacy Policy Our Privacy Policy
Gromco, Inc owns and operates the SiteBits web site. Gromco considers privacy to be an extremely important issue. We are committed to protecting your personal information. Below is an outline of our policy.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers, SiteBits uses log files and records
IP addresses, browser types, referring/exit pages and similar information to analyze trends, administer the site and track users' movements in the aggregate. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Most web browsers will accept cookies by default, but they can be set to reject cookies, either from all websites or from specific sites. You can also manually delete cookies from your web browser. These options are generally set through a "Privacy" setting in your browser setup.
Third Party Advertising
The ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered through our business partners, including Google AdSense, ADSDAQ and other third-party networks. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our partners may place or recognize a unique cookie in your browser. This information is used to serve ads to you.
Third Party Cookies
Some of our advertising partners may use cookie information to serve you ads tailored to your interests.
Note, however, that Gromco, Inc has no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement only covers the use of cookies by Gromco, Inc and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
For more information on Google's use of cookies, please consult:
www.google.com/privacy.html
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Gromco may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of our web sites. We may use any and all information we collect to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may transfer personal information we collected if this web site or Gromco, Inc as a whole is acquired by or merged with another company.
Security of Data
Gromco has taken measures to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. Gromco's networking systems include standard networking equipment designed to prevent unauthorized access to any information stored within our network. All information is regularly backed up and copies are stored at a secure location.
Advertising
Copyright © 2003-2012 Gromco, Inc.
Contact Us
Linking Policy
Photo Licensing
Privacy Policy
